Listen up, because you don't know this one.
atento porque esta no te la sabes muchas
You often say, "Hey, I want a better image,"
veces dices Oye Quiero una imagen mejor
and how do you improve images? Well, you
y cómo mejoras las imágenes pues Se le
ask, and I don't just say it, I do it. "Hey, chat, draw me
pide y no lo digo lo hago Oye chat
a race car." Here's the
dibújame un coche de carreras aquíes el
race car. Pablo: "No, no, no. Make it
coche de carreras Pao no no no Hazlo
much better."
mucho
Here you go, Pablo. I like it,
mejor Aquí tienes Pablo me va molando
but I want it better. I'm asking him. "Hey, chat,
pero lo quiero mejor se lo pido Oye chat
improve it as much as you can, to the maximum.
mejóralo todo lo que puedas al máximo
Here's the race car with the
aquí es el coche de carreras con el
maximum level of detail." Pablo: "It's the
máximo nivel de detalle Pablo Es lo
best you can do. We're not improving,
mejor que se puede hacer no vamos
no, but you want it better? Well, you
mejorando no pero lo quieres mejor pues
ask him, chat." You think you can make it
se lo pides chat Tú crees que puedes
much better, like
hacerlo muchísimo mejor que sea como
those race cars from Need For
esos coches de carreras como Need For
Speed ​​or Fast and Furious, you know, those
Speed o pastan de furius sabes esos
cars that are so cool you'll be blown away? This
coches Tan guapos que los flipas este
race car is inspired by Need For
coche de carreras está inspirado en For
Speed: Fast and Furious, with that
Speed Fast and Furious con ese toque
aggressive touch and full of speed. It's one of those
agresivo y lleno de velocidad es de esos
cars that blows your mind. What do you think now? Well, it's
coches que lo flipas Qué te parece ahora
improving. Well, I want you to
bueno va mejorando Bueno quiero que lo
improve it to the max, use all the
mejores a tope que utilices todos los
resources you have. Give me a moment and I'll do it.
recursos que tengas Dame un momento y lo
This one conveys all the feeling of it, damn, it's
hao estee transmite toda la sens deelo
cool, huh? Improve it as much as you
está guapo eh mejóralo todo todo
can. Not improving it a lot, with what
puedas No mejorándolo mucho con Qué
generator model?  What kind of images do you work with, and
modelo generador de imágenes trabajas y
which ones would you be able to generate
con Cuáles serías capaz de generar
images with? Currently, the image generator model I
imágenes actualmente el modelo generador
work with can
de imágenes con el que trabajo es puedo
create images that resemble certain
crear imágenes que se asemejen a ciertos
styles or results that other models,
estilos o resultados que otros modelos
like my Journey stable diffusion, usually
como mi Journey stable diffusion suele
produce. I want you to mix the most
producir quiero que mezcles lo más
powerful thing you have in Dali 3 stable
potente que tengas en Dali 3 stable
diffusion flux and my Journey to create the
diffusion flux y m Journey para crear el
ultimate car. Understood, Pao, what I'll do
coche definitivo entendido Pao que haré
is
es
use it to create that ultimate car you
utilizar para crear ese coche definitivo
're imagining. This way,
que estás imaginando de esta manera
we manage to improve the images without
conseguimos mejorar las imágenes sin
needing to know a lot of
necesidad de conocer un montón de
styles, defects, or anything. We simply
estilos ni defectos ni nada simplemente
ask it, "Improve it, improve it, improve it," and give
le pedimos mejóralo mejóralo mejóralo y
more, and it always gives a little more. It's simply a matter of asking it;
que de más y siempre da un poco más
no code, no
pedírselo ni código ni conocimiento de
graphic design knowledge, nothing. Just say, "Give me more, give me
diseño gráfico ni nada Dile Dame más
more," and it's very obedient. And since I
dame más y perd es muy obediente Y como
already told you that you didn't know this,
ya te he dicho que no te la sabías
leave me a like because now you
déjame un pedazo de like que ahora te la
know, and you're going to improve all
sabes y vas a mejorar un montón todas
the images you generate a lot. Save it so you don't
las imágenes que generes guárdatelo para
forget. Don't be selfish and
que no se te olviden No seas egoísta y
forward it to others; it's going to be a big help to them.
reenvías a otros que les va a segar un
And don't leave  Follow me to
montón y no dejes de seguirme para
keep learning from you.
seguir aprendiendo de ti trata
Artificial intelligence in your daily life
Inteligencia artificial en tu día a día